livewatch.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Monitronics International, Inc. dba Brinks Home Security ("Brinks Home Security" "we," "us," "our" or “Company”) operates a website located at www.brinkshome.com (the "Website") from which users can gather information concerning news and services provided by Brinks Home Security (the "Brinks Home Security Services"). This Brinks Home Security Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you access the Website and when you use Brinks Home Security Services.

## Types of Information Collected From Customers on Website

In order to provide you with the services available through the Website, we may ask that you provide certain personal information. This may include, but is not limited to, your name, home address, phone number, e-mail address, existing account number, and billing and financial information, including your bank account and/or credit card number. You may also choose to provide certain personal information related to friends or family members who you are referring to us. 

More particularly, this policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Brinks Home Security or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**How Brinks Home Security Uses Information Collected From Customers**

When you provide your personal information to Brinks Home Security, you can be assured that it will only be used to support our efforts to provide quality service to you. We may keep information that we collect for an unlimited period of time. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with others, as follows: 

**Internal Business Use.**  Your personal information may be used in numerous aspects in furtherance of our normal business operations, and in our efforts to provide services to you. Although all information submitted or otherwise collected on this Website belongs solely to Brinks Home Security, that information may be shared with any of its respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, limited partners, general partner, officers, agents, employees, representatives, successors and assigns in connection with the use of that information for the purposes for which it was provided. 

**Third Parties.**  In some circumstances, personal information is also shared with certain third parties, such as Brinks Home Security authorized dealers and third-party vendors (including GreenSky, LLC), in connection with the performance of services or completion of transactions provided to you by those third parties. 

**Marketing.**  We may use information provided to us through this Website for advertising or marketing purposes, or to communicate with you from time to time regarding new products, services and special offers. 

**Business Transfers.**  As we develop our business, we might sell, buy or otherwise transfer businesses or assets. In these types of transactions, your personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. 

**Protection of Brinks Home Security and Others.**  We may disclose personal information to others as appropriate when we believe it is necessary in order to comply with legal requirements; protect the rights, property or safety of Brinks Home Security, its customers or others; and for purposes of fraud protection and risk reduction.

### Other Information

If you choose to identify yourself (or otherwise provide us with personal information) when you use our online forms, we will collect (and may retain) any personally identifying information, such as your name, street address, e-mail address, and phone number, and any other information you provide. We will use this information to try to fulfill your request and may use it to provide you with additional information at a later time. We will not disclose such information to third parties, except as specified in this privacy policy. 

If you request information, services, or assistance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties that (in our judgment) are appropriate in order to fulfill your request. If, when you provide us with such information, you specify that you do not want us to disclose the information to third parties, we will honor your request. Note, however, that if you do not provide such information, it may be impossible for us to refer, respond to, or fulfill your request.

## **Collection and Use of Automatically Generated Information**

### General Practices

If you visit our Website to browse, read, or download information, your web browser automatically sends us (and we may retain) information such as the type of browser software and operating system you are using; the date and time you access our Website; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website. 

We will use this information as aggregate data to help us maintain this Website, e.g., to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our Website, to ensure the Website is working properly, and to help us make our Website more accessible and useful. 

We will not use this information to identify individuals, except for Website security or law enforcement purposes.

We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our Website, unless you choose to provide such information.

We do not respond to “do not track” requests.

### IP Addresses

When your web browser or e-mail application requests a web page on the Internet, it automatically provides a computer location where the requested information should be sent. This is called your computer's "IP address." (IP stands for "Internet Protocol.") 

Brinks Home Security receives your IP address each time you visit our Website to browse, read, or download information. Your IP address is not linked to your email address or any other personally identifiable information. It may be used for various purposes, including diagnosing service or technology problems reported by you that are associated with your IP address, and for estimating the total number of users visiting the Website from specific locales, countries or regions of the world.

### Log Files

When a web page on the Website is requested, that request (including the date and time) is logged on our servers with information including the IP address of the computer that requested the page. 

We use log files for debugging and troubleshooting purposes. IP addresses and access times are not linked to your email address or any other personally identifiable information.

### Cookies

If you request certain services from us, Brinks Home Security may then attempt to set cookies on your computer and later access those cookies. Additionally, third-party widgets such as YouTube or Flickr may install cookies depending on their configuration. You can normally refuse cookies by setting preferences in your browser. You do not need to accept cookies in order to use the Brinks Home Security Services. 

A cookie is a small amount of data which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and then stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot obtain information from your hard drive, destroy files, or transmit viruses. 

Each website can send its own cookie to your browser, if your browser's preferences allow it. To protect your privacy, your browser normally only permits a website to access cookies that it has previously sent to you, but not cookies sent to you by other sites. 

**Choices About Cookies:**  You can normally configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you will still be able to use the Brinks Home Security Services. Cookies are used only as an option selected by you that allows us to recall your email address from the cookie that we sent to your computer.

**Google Analytics**

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this Website. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this Website, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other websites they used prior to coming to this Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this Website.  

Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this Website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Website is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Website by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout-instructions.shtml) on your browser.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [pr@brinkshome.com](mailto:pr@brinkshome.com) or write us at: 

Brinks Home Security  
ATTN: Customer Care  
PO Box 814530  
Dallas, TX 75381-4530  

### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.  

 **Personally Identifiable Information of Children**

We do not knowingly solicit or collect the personally identifiable information of children under the age of 18.  If we become aware that we possess the personally identifiable information of any children, we will delete the information from our records.

 **Governing Law**

Our Website is governed solely by the federal and state laws of the United States, and information submitted to our Website is stored on servers located in the United States.  European Union residents are advised not to disclose any personally identifiable information to us.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

Brinks Home Security may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on the Website. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.  

 **Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, would like to review or correct information we have retained about you, or opt out from marketing emails, send an email to [suggestions@brinkshome.com](mailto:suggestions@brinkshome.com)
